who would have thought our brother a
tree
farmer I still can't believe you
actually have a job at the Mont clar
Acres neither can I how much is Bart
will be paying you $12 million oh he's
not paying me in money he's paying me
and Butterfly
Kisses bro you got to find a new job oh
come now I did promise to give your
family $600 of in store credit that you
can use at my store since your brother
did help me plant all these [__]
trees
$600 I like the sound of that maybe
we'll have something left over to spend
in the gift shop that's the spirit old
lady now baby be a cute little elf and
Lead these customers out back to show
them my family's homegrown trees only
the most luscious will
do woohoo every Hedgehog follow me my
[__] I do believe you're forgetting
something you didn't expect to go
outside without your uniform did
youuh
phew oh my is that a jolly elf chalk
full of gingerbread or is that just my
Bach so how does it fit dear I don't
think I gained that much
weight holy [__]
[__] for the rest of the day your name
shall be jingle because of how often you
jingle my balls now go out there and
earn your
key 130,000 bucks Sonic what kind of
scammer you and your boyfriend trying to
pull on your own mother oh golly G Mama
that can't be right luckily here at the
Monclair Acres we have a protocol for
this kind of
thing sis why is my brother over there
acting like a [__] I think he's shaking
his butt to make the Bel ring to Aller B
will be to
trouble my [__] me and Daddy Have Heard
the Bells is someone trying to rape you
because of the sexy leard I made you
well no Bart lebby it's worse I think
there's a pricing error on all the
merchandise pricing error no that's not
possible I wrote them all by hand with
my daddy you can't charge that much what
about the inflation crisis in America
with these prices no one will be able to
have a Christmas this year so what I'm a
billionaire when inflation goes up who
do you think gets the money if you
really want one so bad ask my dad and
maybe he'll buy one for you Mr Monclair
will you buy us a Christmas
tree Bartle be I know it's a lot to ask
no it's not especially on Christmas Eve
but can you start paying me money for my
service I've been working at the street
farm for 8 hours a day 365 days a year
for the last 4 Years bro you got to find
a new job [__] I care about you I do
and that's why you're going to give my
family a free Christmas tree F no I
threw in a section for poor people right
over
there what about this one knuckles it
has only four pins so we can't hang any
ornaments off of it what about hanging a
car air freshener that will help s our
house smells really bad I want to go
home but are you sure if we put this
stick on the away our descendants just
may be lucky enough to pay it off by the
year
3,849 it's not the tree it's because of
the multi-billionaire over there eating
fi Alfredo he chuggles every time we
turn our backs because we in the poor
section well the Montclair are [__]
[__] they also tried to tax my father
who was also poor so he couldn't pay
them their family came to our house and
beheaded my own father in the front lawn
the whole town is in the poor section
because bleby used his financial
influence to cut down the rest of the
trees in town so the people would have
no choice but to buy on me his trees
well good on him I'm happy to see an
entreprenur go out and reach for his
dream even while he is destroying poor
people's lives in the process well maybe
most poor people like you would be
happier if you were as dedicated as baby
instead of just blaming rich people for
your own laziness and
failures smart grandson you got there
perhaps you should be taking notes
fool I I mean it's good enough for bleby
so it's good enough for us too
put your back into it these trees aren't
going to load themselves ladies the
overlord of the monk L Acres could catch
us any minute and God knows we don't got
the money to put this [__] on lay
away I don't get it sleep why are moving
back in with Dr Robotnik didn't you like
living in a one room apartment in the
[__] GTO the gunshots were like free
music [__] you can't even use the
bathroom correctly yes I can when I got
a pee PE I use a toilet just like
everybody else and when someone else is
already using the toilet I po pee on the
floor outside the bathroom and then the
one coming out has to clean it up Jesus
Christ I have to cut the cheese like
really really bad if I roll off the
window out of nowhere will my evil
bounty hunters know I only did it to
cover up a big stink oh [__] it they
probably won't even
notice
there he goes again he's probably
letting one rip out of his ass right now
I hope he doesn't get Hy poop on my Long
John Silvers in the back seat hey Patty
thought you could let one RI and make
off with one of my pris
huh get out of my way you [__]
idiots Barby found
me
impossible he's able to match my truck's
speed of 120 mph and he's only walking
this is no man this is
[Music]
God please don't kill me Bartleby I had
every intention of paying you I swear I
was only going home to get my wallet
naturally for this is one of the finest
trees on the lot what was it again 12 no
18 trillion oh Mr mler won't you spare
some of your Christmas Mercy I'll never
be able to pay that off with my job at
Walgreens well lucky you I think I know
one way to clear your debt just as long
as it doesn't involve wearing a green
leotard all righty but Nick for the rest
of the day you want a snowflake I want
you to go around and serve nice cold
eggnog to our guests you expect me to
cater drinks in this thing do you know
who I am some fat guy in a n suit I'm
the Dominator of Worlds and Overlord of
all that is diabolical I can't go around
serving holiday drinks in an undersized
Christmas
leotard hey no taking pictures of the
merchandise oh how the mighty have
fallen I was going to send letter to
Santa but why bother no present is going
to top seeing you in that [__] get up
you piece of
[__]
well go on snowflake don't keep my uncle
waiting
forever my Bach would you be a dull and
to a pine tree seed over here real quick
this family is looking for a brand new
tree and they sh Wait a second longer
one SE on the
house
that blonde man just made a pine tree
grow with nothing but his fist of course
he did [__] Barby punched the seed into
the ground with such force that it
created a ripple in SpaceTime so the
tiny little seed felt 50 years pass in 9
billionth of a m e second but the sky is
overcast wouldn't the seed need sunlight
and water to grow damn I had no idea I
married a [__] woman listen pitch
the the pressure of barnab fist was so
powerful that it melted the surrounded
snow and the sunlight glistened through
barnel's golden hair making the sea grow
you stupid idiot enough chitchat the
deal is sealed now day up oh right here
you go
$10 and what are the rest of the money
we were hoping we could put this tree on
lay away and pay for it later like what
they do at Kmart does this Farm look
like a Kmart to you not really but all
we have is
$10 24 hours that's how long you have to
make up the rest of the money otherwise
your son will be sent across state lines
to Ohio never to be seen
again well knuckles I am afraid that's
as far as these old legs will carry my
fat ass let's return to our futuristic
mobian car and go home but
great-grandfather what about the
Christmas tree you promised miss me
maybe next year Knuckles when literally
anyone else that isn't Bartleby is
selling Christmas
trees hey hands off the goods pan bro go
ask Bartleby to give us a tree even if
it's just our family but if he gives us
a tree then he would have to give
everyone a tree bro if we don't get a
tree Santa Won't knowwhere to drop off
his presence and you can kiss that
Minecraft leg go said goodbye Bart leby
um I hope it's not a lot to ask but can
my family please have a tree that's
quite the tall order let me discuss this
with my parents what did that little
[__] say he wants a Christmas tree
mother what say you well we haven't sold
a single [__] tree we might as well
give him one for publicity purposes
thanks for your input mother I will take
that consideration into
account so does this mean we can have a
tree I don't know can we have 20 ,000
bucks kids I'm heating up the car make
one more pass around the farm if you
want but we got to go but we still
haven't picked out a Christmas tree
nobody in town has forget it Sonia this
Christmas is
over another job well done [__] tally
up the numbers how much did we make
today [__] 0 surely you mean five with
N9 zeros after that for 5 billion no
just 0 just like every other day for the
past four years but I marked down all of
the trees by $2 maybe they just didn't
notice oh they noticed they just didn't
have $89 million to spend for our
cheapest tree looks like there will be
no Christmas this year all because of us
no it's all because of you because you
weren't able to convince a single soul
to buy my [__] now get the hell off my
acers y
jingle
leave well snowlake looks like it's just
you and me now tie up all the tries and
haul them inside we'll try it again next
year no we ain't I'm not working for you
what I'm saying I
quit no you don't because you're fire
you still have to give me my two weeks
notice for first I know my laws you
don't know a [__] fat ass the only thing
on your mind is the price of a Little
Caesar's
beater fine then I didn't have anybody
when I was a wee baby and I sure as hell
don't need anybody now Mama huh mama
papa where have you
gone they left a note I bet they went to
freshen up before dinner
we left to spend Christmas in Hawaii
because we don't love you we are however
afraid of you so we left a little
spending money it's not much only $560
trillion but it's all we had in our
pockets at the time so we pray to God
that it is enough for you not to hunt us
down XOXO no seriously we don't love
you poor people will never understand my
pain was the Night Before Christmas when
all through the house no creature was
having a dialogue not even a
hedgehog bro do you think Santa will
still bring us
presents how can he how can one even
have a Christmas without a Christmas
tree you are right manic I am a fool for
even thinking such a thing Wednesday
Christmas as we know it is over
forever there you are [__] wait where's
my
[Music]
tree it is unfortunate that Christmas
was cancelled money isn't everything out
there we still have all these beautiful
Christmas lights Bart ly can't take it
from
us hey why did the neighborhood go dark
what happened to all of the Christmas
lights has the Rapture begun has the
Lord returned to save us from ble be
[__] the city is cutting coughs by
making everyone turn their lights off by
7 something about the M Lair family
using too much of the city's electricity
to power their own Christmas
[Music]
lights well at least one person is
enjoying himself on Christmas Eve here's
to a Merry [__] Christmas
kids kids hurry downstairs I think
there's a Christmas tree a Christmas
tree I don't believe it come on Manic
Sonic let's go yes children Christmas
isn't cancelled after
[Music]
all usely
home oh hell no this [__] really doing
this it's bleby he's just trying to
humiliate us even
[Music]
further oh my sweet darling wife I pray
that you are in hell so you don't have
to look down from heaven and see this
steaming pile of
[Music]
[__] it feels nice to do a bit of
charity work on Christmas Eve
I think I'll head down and pay the town
as a visit I can't wait to see all of
the young ones cheerful faces when they
realize I snuck into all of their houses
and gave each and every one of them a
free trve from my
farm damn it John what did your father
and I tell you about bringing trash into
the house but it wasn't me mommy some
sexy man dropped it off at the back door
with this handwritten letter a
handwritten letter who in the right mind
would be right you nobody loves you I
noticed you were at my Christmas Tre
Farm today but didn't buy anything so I
looked in new bank account and noticed
that you didn't have enough I wanted to
do the right thing so take all of the
money out of your bank account which
wasn't enough for the trip and gave you
one anyway Merry Christmas Daddy what
will we do now that our bank account is
empty how will we eat and what a grandpa
he's in the hospital with
cancer he's 97 s let him
[Music]
go
happy happy merry Christmas happy happy
Merry Christmas to
[Music]
you when it's coldside and the down I
hear Jingle Bells as the stars go by I
good c e and milk and
Candy present wa under the
tree it's
Christmas la la la it's Christmas time
la la la Jesus Born To Us savior of the
world it's Christmas time la la la it's
Christmas time la la la Jesus was born
to
it's Christmas
time happy happy merry Christmas happy
happy Merry Christmas to
you
you Mary and Jose had a baby and came
from far to see shephers heard the
Angels Sing
glory to God for the new
king it's Christmas
time it's Christmas time la la Jesus was
Bor to
usor of the
world it's Christmas time la la la it's
Christmas time la la la Jesus was born
to
us it's Christmas
happy happy merry Christmas happy happy
Merry Christmas to
you to
you happy happy merry Christmas happy
happy Merry Christmas to
you to you and you and you
[Music]
you
[Applause]
w